This is your food.
Begin your house.
Can we show them how to treat you fine?
I want to treat you fine.
It is a case in that you read it once you are ready, we can start.
My feet are driving me crazy.
Can you give me something to fix it quickly?
My name is Naga.
My medical number is your 234567.
My age is 50 years.
Before I recommend anything, could you please answer a few questions?
Sure.
Can you describe more about all the sentences that you have?
I have flaking and itchiness between the toes.
Okay.
What do you think might have caused the sentence and how would have the sentence been?
I'm not very sure maybe because of working a long day in the arts and in the farm.
Okay.
Do you have experience fever, swollen glands?
No, okay.
Is your first time having this sentence?
Yeah.
Okay.
Have you tried any medication so far?
No.
No, right?
Do you have any medical conditions or allergies?
I am allergic to peanuts.
Peanut, it's okay.
Are you currently taking any over-the-counter medication?
What about supplement vitamin or herb products?
No.
No, alright.
So just the itchiness of your feet.
Okay, it seems to me that, based on your information, it seems to me that you are having tinnia.
And we do have topical cream.
Is there anything else that you need?
No, then I recommend the Contrerasol 1% cream.
And you have to apply the cream two times a day to your affected area.
And do remember to continue to use the cream 14 days after your symptoms have disappeared.
And develop a stick to prevent recurrence.
And some of the common side effects include the mild burning sensation and redness of the skin, but usually quite well tolerated.
So don't worry, but if your side fit are very severe, do consult a doctor immediately.
Is my explanation clear for you?
Okay, do you have any other questions for me?
But you might repeat what I said just now.
He understood all the information.
Okay.
Other than taking medication, I will also advise you to wear breathable clothing and especially breathable shoes and to prevent the recurrence in future.
And you should also avoid going to the swimming pool area barefoot.
Is it all right for you?
Here's a recent information about the management here.
Do remember to come back to me or see a doctor if your condition still does not improve after one week of using this Cochraneazole 1% cream.
Do you have any other questions for me?
Then here's your medication.
I hope you'll recover soon.
Do feel free to come back to us or contact us if you have any other concerns.
th